{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2060","name":"Westside Academy Alternative Education","address":"4701 McKinley St","zipcode":"48208","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"072452","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"210.0","coords":"-83.10332,42.34221","geojson":{"id":"2060","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.103316594,42.3422085660001]},"properties":{"name":"Westside Academy Alternative Education","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","address":"4701 McKinley St","zipcode":"48208","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"072452","establishmentid":"2060","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/15/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"526","name":"Vicki's Bar-B-Que","address":"3845 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"4754","name":"Southwest Detroit Community School (K-8)","address":"4001 29th St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3865","name":"Monte Bello Pizzeria","address":"5181 Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"4459","name":"Legend's Coney Island","address":"5210 W Grand River","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"4572","name":"Legends Grill","address":"5210 Grand River","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"4326","name":"Hazel's Place","address":"5516 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3854","name":"Salvation Army #2","address":"3737 Lawton","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"3855","name":"Salvation Army #3","address":"3737 Lawton","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"5064","name":"Salvation Army Truck #12","address":"3737 Lawton ","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"3853","name":"Salvation Army #1","address":"3737 Lawton","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"3856","name":"Salvation Army #4","address":"3737 Lawton","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"2727","name":"Salvation Army","address":"3737 Lawton","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"5171","name":"La Noria Bistro","address":"5517 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48213"},{"establishmentid":"3443","name":"El Barzon Restaurante","address":"3710 Junction Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"604","name":"Mike's Famous Ham Place","address":"3700 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"1527","name":"Ferguson Building","address":"2750 Selden St","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"5285","name":"Hope of Detroit Academy Mid/High School","address":"4444 35th Street","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"595","name":"Hy-Grade Delicatessen Restaurant, Inc.","address":"3640 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"546","name":"Hope of Detroit Academy","address":"4443 N Campbell St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"4673","name":"Covenant Central-Covenent House Michigan","address":"2959 Martin Luther King ","zipcode":"48208"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42466","inspectionDate":"2018-06-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Paper towel dispenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40393","inspectionDate":"2017-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Paper towel dispenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"44692","inspectionDate":"2017-06-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Beverage container","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep covered."}]},{"inspectionid":"37359","inspectionDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"THERMOMETER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate in accordance with manufacturer specifications."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (milk)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2060"}}